好了  不准偷看
All right, no peeking.
不准偷看
No peeking.
No peeking. No peeking!
好  不过我睁眼时  你最好还穿着衣服
All right, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes.
好了  睁眼
All right. Open your eyes!
圣母啊  所有纯正而美好的东西
Sweet mother of all that is good and pure!
《我们的日子》跟我续约了
Days of our Lives picked up my option!
-恭喜  -我知道
- Congratulations! - I know!
在我们终于可以像样地看《绿色田野》了
Now we can finally watch Green Acres the way it was meant to be seen.
哪一张是我的
So which one is mine?
随你选  随你选
Whichever one you want, man. Whichever one you want!
那张不行
Not that one.
帅
Oh, yes!
帅  这才叫生活
Oh, yeah! That's the stuff.
敢不敢
Do we dare?
敢
We dare.
真不敢相信  两条牛牺牲了自己的性命
I can't believe two cows made the ultimate sacrifice...
是为了成全你们跷起腿来看电视
...so you could watch TV with your feet up.
不  它们本来就是椅子形状的牛
No, they were chair-shaped cows.
根本不可能在野外存活
They never would have survived in the wild.
屏幕真炫  迪克·范·戴克看起来很逼真
This screen is amazing. Dick Van Dyke is practically life-size.
露丝·玛丽不该上这么大的荧幕  对不对
Rose Marie really belongs on a smaller screen, doesn't she?
各位
Hi, you guys.
好呀
Hey, you.
你今天怎么样
So, uh, how was your day?
还是老样子
You know, pretty much the usual.
晴空万里  鸟儿欢唱
Sun shining, birds chirping.
真的  我今天也是
Really? Mine too.
不错  我今天也是
Hey, cool! Mine too!
这下可好  我得去馆里一趟
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got to get to the museum.
-那我们今晚见  -好
- So I'll see you tonight? - O.K.
再见  各位
Bye, guys!
今晚
Tonight?
-今晚怎么了  -我们第一次正式约会
- What's tonight? - It is our first official date.
第一次约会
Our first date.
喂
Hello?
今晚你要在我承办的派对上替我跑堂的
Tonight you're supposed to waitress for me, my catering thing?
我的话有没有让你想起什么
Any of those words trigger anything for you?
天啊  摩妮卡  我忘了
Oh, God, Monica. I forgot!
这是我们的第一次约会
This is our first date.
-但这工作是我妈帮我找的  -我可以当服务生
- Yes, but my mom got me this job. - I can be a waitress!
谢谢  谢谢  看到吗  还有菲比
Thank you, thank you. See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
真的  菲菲  你必须来真的
Really, Pheebs? You'd have to be an actual waitress.
这可不是办家家酒
This can't be like your "I can be a bear cub" thing.
我可以当服务生  瞧我的
I can be a waitress. Okay, watch this.
给我两份一号餐  不要培根
Give me two number ones, 86 the bacon...
一份双蛋吐司  要炒蛋
...one Adam and Eve on a raft and wreck them!
是詹姆斯·邦德
It's James Bond!
-抱歉来迟了  -没关系  请进
- Sorry we're late. - That's okay. Come on in.
对不起  摩妮卡·盖勒来不来  我听说她要来
Um, I'm sorry, is Monica Geller coming? I was told she was.
伯克医生  是我
Dr. Burke, it's me.
你是摩妮卡
Monica?
老天  你以前好...
My God! You used to be so....
你一定是减了...
I mean, you've You must have lost like....
你美极了
You look great.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是我朋友菲比  她今天晚上来帮忙
This is my friend Phoebe. She's gonna be helping me tonight.
菲比  幸会
Hi Phoebe, nice to meet you.
-你近来如何  -很好  很好  你呢
- So how you been? - I've been great, just great. How have you been?
你大概也知道  我跟芭芭拉分手了
Obviously you know Barbara and I split up...
不然你也不会歪着头来问我
otherwise you wouldn't have done the head tilt.
歪头
The head tilt?
对  自从离了婚  当别人向我问好时
Yeah, since the divorce, when anybody asks me how I am,
总是同情地歪头问  "你好吗  不要紧吧"
it's always with a sympathetic head tilt.  'How ya doin'? You OK?'
对不起
I'm sorry.
不  没关系  相信我  我也一样
No. It's fine. Believe me, I do it too.
我总是以点头来表示  "我没事"
I always answer with the "I'm okay" head bob. "I'm okay."
"你确定"
"You're sure?"
"对  我没事"
"Yeah, I'm fine."
听着  我得去放音乐了  我有个自动换碟机
Hey listen, I've got to set up the music.  I got a new CD changer.
当然了  离婚害我只剩四张碟可换了
Of course, the divorce only left me with four CDs to change.
真不幸
That's too bad.
死不了的
I'll survive.
两份大号  都要另加奶酪
Two larges, extra cheese on both.
听着
But listen...
别按19号的门铃
...don't ring the buzzer for 19.
按20号  盖勒和格林公寓
Ring 20. Geller/Greene.
她们会开门  懂吗
They'll let you in, okay?
按我们的门铃就没小费
If you buzz our door, there's no tip for you.
好  谢了
Okay, thanks.
披萨马上就来  我说我们不用起来了吧
Pizza's on the way. I told you we wouldn't have to get up.
如果要尿尿呢
What if we have to pee?
那我不点汽水了
I'll cancel the sodas.
你必须进去  这是你的派对
Get back out there. It's your party!
可是他们好没劲  全都是眼科医生
But they're so dull! They're all ophthalmologists.
你就是眼科医生
You're an ophthalmologist.
因为我随了父母的心愿  我其实想当警长
Because my parents wanted me to be. I wanted to be a sheriff.
真好笑  白内衣  白内障  我懂了  不  我懂了
That's funny. Cadillac, cataract. I get it.t, no I get it,
你别跟着进来
But you stay out there!
-瞧  -好  这样吧
- You see? - All right. I tell you what.
五分钟后我来叫你  就说烤肉出了问题
I'll come get you in five minutes with some sort of kebob emergency.
好吧  你最好这么做
OK. You better.
天  我去了
Oh, God, here we go.
要看他们发狂吗
Hey, want to see them go nuts?
瞧我的
Watch this.
谁要眼镜
Who needs glasses?
你好神魂颠倒
You are so smitten.
我才没有
I am not!
你是只神魂颠倒的小猫咪
Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten.
-你应该约他  -伯克医生吗
- You should ask him out. - Dr. Burke?
不太合适  他可是个大人
I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grownup.
所以呢  你们两个互有好感
So? You two are totally into each other.
菲比  他是我父母的朋友
Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents.
他比我大20岁
He's like 20 years older than me.
那你就再也不跟他见面了
OK, so what, you're just never gonna see him again?
不是永远
Not never.
我明天约好了  要去他那里检查眼睛
I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.
-你不是才检查过眼睛吗  -是啊  但是
- Didn't you just get your eyes checked? - Yeah, but you know...
27是个
... 27 is...
眼病高发年龄
...a dangerous eye age.
我不是说这部电影不好
C'mon, I'm not saying it was a bad movie,
我只是说这部电影有一点
I'm just saying it was a little...
难懂
... hard to follow.
我说过会有字幕的
I told you there was going to be subtitles.
我知道
I know.
我只是不想在第一次约会就戴眼镜
I just didn't want to wear my glasses on our first date.
摩妮卡
Monica?
我亲你时  你不叫我老妹的名字会比较有情调
It would really help when I'm kissing if you didn't shout my sister's name.
亲爱的  我只是检查一下
Honey, I'm just checking.
-摩妮卡  -摩妮卡
- Monica? - Mon?
摩妮卡
Monica?
怎么了
What, what?
抱歉  天呐  抱歉
I'm sorry. Oh, god. I'm sorry.
对不起  只是当你的手滑到我屁股上时
It's just, when you moved your hands down to my butt...
感觉就像"罗斯在摸我屁股"
...it was, like, "Whoa! Ross' hands are on my butt!"
-抱歉  -这很好笑吗
- I'm sorry. - And that's funny. Why?
不好笑
Well, it's not.
对不起  我想我只是有点紧张
I'm sorry. I guess I'm just nervous.
对象是你
I mean, it's you.
是我们俩
You know, it's us.
我们在越过那条线  这不是小事
We're crossing that line. It's sort of a big thing.
我知道是大事  只是不知道有"哈哈"这么大
Well, I know it's big. I just didn't know it was ha-ha big.
我的手没靠近你的屁股
Okay, my hands were nowhere near your butt.
我知道
I know, I know, I know!
我只是在想你的手上次在那里那回
I was thinking about when they were there the last time.
对不起  听着  我保证
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Okay, look! I promise.
我会忍住  不会再乱笑了  把手放回去
I'm good, I'm not gonna laugh anymore. OK put your hands back there.
不行  我做不到
No, see, now I can't.
我觉得太不自然了
because uh, I'm feeling too self conscious.
就半边屁股
Just one cheek.
不  我没感觉了
Nuh, uh, the moment's gone.
把手伸出来  我自己靠过去
Alright, just put your hands out and I'll back up into them.
那还挺浪漫
That's romantic.
-来吧  摸一下  -不要
- C'mon touch it. - No.
-来吧  捏一下  -不要
- Oh, come on, squeeze it. - No!
-揉呢  -不要
- Rub it? - No.
快来  抓我屁股好吗
Oh, come on! Would you just grab my ass?
你瞧瞧  车子起火了
Wow! Look at that! The car is on fire...
可是它那昂贵的油漆
...yet somehow its expensive paint job...
却被奇迹车蜡保护得完好无损
...is protected by the Miracle Wax.
你脸上有个"奇多脆"  老兄
You've got a Cheeto on your face, man.
你来干什么  不是要跟瑞秋出去吗
What're you doin' here? Aren't you supposed to be out with Rachel?
那是14个小时前
That was 14 hours ago.
那结果如何
So how'd it go?
听着  你们有没有试过  跟一个女孩亲热
Oh. Listen, have you ever been, you know, fooling around with a girl...
然后她笑了起来
...and she started laughing?
有  不过那是1982年
Yeah, but it was 1982...
我的"天地一群鸥"发型让她的下巴发痒
...and my Flock of Seagulls haircut was tickling her chin.
她嘲笑你吗
She laughed at you?
我从九年级的打字课起  就想这一刻了
I've been wanting this since ninth grade typing.
我只是希望一切能完美
And I just want it to be perfect...
顺利  还有...
...and right and....
激光束为什么切不断油漆
Why isn't that laser beam cutting through the paint?
-是奇迹车蜡的关系  -那绝对是一项奇迹
- It's the Miracle Wax! - lt certainly is a miracle.
各位
Hi, you guys.
听着  我在想...
Listen, I was thinking about....
听着  你们可以大声点吗
Listen. Can you guys speak up?
你们放低声音  我们反而更听不清
It's harder for us to hear you when you lower your voice.
听我说  昨晚的事很抱歉  我真的很想补偿你
O.K. Listen. I'm sorry about last night. I really want to make it up to you.
你没必要补偿我
There's no need to make it up
怎么补偿
How?
我在想  或许来顿浪漫晚餐
Well, I was thinking maybe a romantic dinner...
配上烛光美酒
...with candles and wine.
然后要不回我那边去
And then maybe going back to my place...
品尝点心
...for dessert.
听起来
That sounds...
很完美
... perfect?
干什么
What's this?
帮忙买两瓶啤酒好吗
Would you get us a couple of beers?
我现在要看你的眼睛了
I'm going to look into your eyes now.
真的
Really?
对  那是我的工作
Yeah. That's my job.
好
All right.
看上面
Look up.
看下面
Look down.
张开眼睛  看下面
Now, open your eyes and look down.
对
That's right.
看光线这里
Look into the light.
现在看我
Now look at me.
好
OK.
你眼睛不错  很健康的眼睛
Your eyes look good. Those are good eyes.
很好  它们觉得很好
Good. They feel good.
在我头上
In my head.
-见到你真好  -彼此
- So, it's great to see ya. - You too.
彼此
You too.
好  再见了
O.K. Goodbye.
-眼药水  -什么
- Drops! - What?
眼药水  给  免费的
Drops. Here, they're free.
谢了
Thanks.
我该走了
So, I guess I better be going.
对  改天见
Yeah, I'll see you later.
再次感谢你
Thanks again.
我们得把你们这两只懒虫弄起来
We have to get you lazy boys out of these chairs.
你们应该走出去  跟三维世界的人打交道
You should go outside and be with the three-dimensional people.
不  在里面好
No. Inside good.
在外面坏
Outside bad.
你们真是太可悲了
You guys are so pathetic.
仙纳度
Oh, Xanadu!
她也加入我们了
She's one of us now.
各位
Hi you guys.
我们只是想过来跟各位道晚安
We just wanted to stop by and say good night.
晚安
Good night.
你瞧瞧  他们连头都不回
Look at that, they won't even turn their heads.
好了  各位  我要脱上衣了
All right, you guys. I'm taking off my shirt.
她说谎
She's lying.
别再叫吃的去我们家
Stop sending food to our apartment!
摩妮卡  打扮得这么美干什么
Mon, why are you dressed up?
今晚又不是只有你有约会
You're not the only one who has a date tonight.
- 什么  你有约会  跟谁  - 没有谁
- What? You have a date? Who with? - No one.
说嘛  他叫什么名字
Come on, what's his name?
没什么
Nothing.
别卖关子了
Come on, tell me.
好吧  不过这件事  我非常兴奋  懂吗
All right, but I'm very excited about this, okay?
你得保证  你不会摆出大哥架子来教训我
So promise you won't get big-brothery and judgmental.
我保证  是谁
I promise. What?
-是理查德·伯克  -理查德·伯克是谁
- It's Richard Burke. - Who's Richard Burke?
伯克医生
Dr. Burke?
你要跟理查德·伯克医生约会  为什么  为什么...
You have a date with Dr. Burke? Why? Why? Why...
我会不高兴呢
...should that bother me?
我爱他  他就像...
I love that man. He's like a...
爸爸的兄弟
...a brother to Dad.
告诉你吧  他是我交往过的
Well for your information he happens to be one of
最聪明  最成熟  最性感的男人
the brightest, most sophisticated, sexiest men I've ever been with.
伯克医生性感
Dr. Burke is sexy?
天啊  当之无愧
Oh, God! Absolutely!
该死
Damn!
又是馆里找我  我可以...
It's the museum again. Can I?
-伯克医生亲过我一次  -什么时候
- Dr. Burke kissed me once. - When?
我七岁时  我骑自行车在他家门前摔了跤
When I was 7, I crashed my bike right out in front of his house...
为了让我不继续哭  他亲了我这里
...and to stop me from crying, he kissed me right here.
-你好幸运  -我知道
- Oh, you are so lucky! - I know.
南方古猿不应该在那个展区的
Australopithecus isn't supposed to be in that display.
不  能人是直立的
No, Homo habilis was erect.
南方古猿从来都没能完全直立
Australopithecus was never fully erect.
或许他是紧张罢了
Well, maybe he was nervous.
看  搞什么鬼
Oh, look! I can't believe this!
能人根本还没学会使用工具
Look, homo-habilus hasn't even learned how to use tools yet
他们竟然还给他陶罐
and they've got him here wi, with clay pots.
不如给他一个微波炉算了
Why don't they just give him a microwave?
抱歉  我花了那么多时间
I'm sorry, I'm sorry this is taking so long, ya know,
这比我想像的还花时间  我们会吃晚饭的
I, I, it's just it's longer than I expected, we will have dinner.
没关系  不要紧
It's O.K., it's fine.
卡尔
Karl!
天啊
Oh, God.
-那是米歇尔吗  -对
- Wow! Is that Michelle? - Yep.
高中毕业后就没见过她了
I've not seen her since high-school graduation.
老天  那天晚上她醉得好...
Oh, my God, that night she got so dru...
激动
Emotional.
她又要生了
You know, she's having another baby.
-我以为她才刚生过  -不  亨利快两岁了
- I thought she just had one. - No, no. Henry's almost 2.
他讲话什么的都会  看
And he's talking and everything. Here.
前几天他告诉我  他喜欢我胜过他的爷爷
The other day he told me he liked me better than his other grandpa.
公平说来  他的爷爷是酒鬼  但还是...
In all fairness, his other grandpa's a drunk, but still....
你是个爷爷
You're a grandpa.
是的
Yeah.
我们疯了吗
Are we nuts here?
我不知道  或许
I don't know. Maybe.
我在你游泳池里尿过尿  现在却在和你约会
I mean, I'm dating a man whose pool I once peed in.
我不需要知道这些
I didn't need to know that.
21年是差太多了
I guess 21 years is a lot.
见鬼  我能喝酒的时候你才刚出生
I mean, hell, I'm a whole person who can drink older than you.
对
Yeah.
那...
So.
那或许我们应该就...
So maybe we should just....
对  大概吧
Yeah, yeah, maybe.
太糟了
This really sucks.
可不是吗
Yeah, it sure does.
我们不用现在就决定什么  对吧
We don't really have to decide anything right now, do we?
对  我们一点都不用急
No, there's no rush or anything.
-送披萨的  -我要杀了那两个人
- Pizza delivery! - Oh, I'm gonna kill those guys!
瑞秋  我好了
Rach. I'm done.
对  不过那家餐厅也打烊了
Yeah, well, you know what? So is Sorentino's.
什么  对不起  我们要不去别家餐厅好了
Wha, OK, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.
还是算了  很晚了  所有餐厅都打烊了
No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed.
我们改天晚上再吃好了
Why don't we just do it another night?
不  不要
No, no, we won't.
不要
We won't?
跟我来
Come on.
那是死的  对吧
Okay, that's dead, right?
这是干什么  我们在干什么
What is this? What are we doing?
-你要红莓苹果还是红莓葡萄  -葡萄
- Do you want Cranapple or Cran-Grape? - Grape.
好了  现在
Okay, now...
坐下  好的
...sit. OK.
天啊
Oh, my God!
数十亿年前  地球只是...
Billions of years ago, Earth was only...
抱歉
Sorry.
现在放映的是什么
So what are we looking at?
你看那边  那一大团旁边那一小堆星星
Well, you see that little cluster of stars next to the big one?
那是大熊座
That is Ursa Major.
-真的  -我不知道  有可能
- Really? - No idea. It could be.
听着  抱歉我今晚必须工作
Listen, I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
你值得我等
You were worth the wait.
我指的不只是今晚
And I don't just mean tonight.
你没笑
You're not laughing.
这次没那么好笑了
This time it's not so funny.
天啊
Oh, God!
亲爱的
Honey?
没关系
That's okay.
什么
What?
你误会了  你刚刚压到的是果汁盒
Oh, no. You just rolled over the juice box.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
早呀
Hey, you.
真不敢相信我会在你身边醒来
I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.
我知道  是很不可思...
I know. It is pretty unbel...
-怎么了  -这里还有别人
- What? - We're not alone.
-是火警在响吗  -是
- Is that the fire alarm? - Yeah.
还没变热  还有时间
It's not warm yet. We still have time.
-酷  -对  酷
-Cool. -Yeah, yeah. Cool!